hirehive.io 2019-11-11

# Privacy Policy details - HireHive Recruiting Software

This Privacy Policy applies to the websites: www.hirehive.com owned and operated by HireHive. This Privacy Policy describes how HireHive collects, uses, shares and secures the personal information you provide, as well as the candidate data transferred to us for processing on behalf of our customers. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information.

Please read the below carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data.

### **Keeping your data private**

HireHive is based in the EU (Cork, Ireland) and we store all data on servers that are physically located in the EU. We are in full compliance with General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and Irish Data Protection directives. We store our data on Microsoft’s cloud platform Azure – in their ‘North Europe’ data centre located in Dublin, Ireland.

Our customers trust is our main priority. If you have any questions regarding data security and privacy please contact us at [datasec@hirehive.com](mailto:datasec@hirehive.com)

### **Information collected**

We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. We collect the details provided by you together with other information we learn about you from your use of the service and your visits to our web sites. We may also monitor site usage to enable us improve the service we provide.

### **Information we may collect from you**

We may collect and process the following information from you the customer:  
Information that you provide to us by filling in forms on our website www.hirehive.com This includes the information provided by you at the time of registering for an account on our site, subscribing to our service, subscribing to our blog or requesting further information or services from us.

**Collection:**

We may collect the following personal information from you:

  * Contact Information, such as name, email address, mailing address, or phone number;
  * Billing Information, such as credit card number and billing address;
  * Unique Identifiers, such as username, account number or password;
  * Geolocation based on IP address;
  * Information about your business, such as company name, business type.
  * Demographic information, such as age, education, gender, interests and zip code (from candidates)

If you are a Candidate, we will record information relating to your previous and current employment, skills and experience and CV/resume that you upload to the Website.

If you are a Customer, we may record information regarding your job Openings and other details regarding your organisation and its personnel including, but not limited to: a company overview, company logo, staff email addresses and correspondence, social platforms as provided by you and your website.

If you contact us via email or within the system through a third party app, we may keep a record of that correspondence for a reasonable time in order for us to respond to your query.

Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, and the resources that you access.

### **Purpose and Use of Your Information**

We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

If you believe that one of your contacts has provided us with your personal information and you would like to request that it be removed from our database, please contact us at the contact information below.

We will use your personal information to provide our service. We will also use your contact details to communicate with you. We like to hear your views to help us improve our service. From time to time we may contact you by email to ask for your opinions. You can opt out of this at any time by contacting us.

### **Information Sharing**

We may share your information with third parties who provide services on our behalf to help with our business activities. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us, to which these services may include:

  * Payment processing
  * Providing customer service platform
  * Sending marketing communications – ie. our monthly recruiting newsletter
  * Providing cloud computing infrastructure

### **Disclosure of Your Information**

Information that you submit to us will be used solely for the purpose of offering you a service and will not be shared with any third party that is not explicitly listed here.  
As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site.

HireHive uses cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.

Approved Sub-Processors  
The following Sub-Processors shall be considered approved by the Data Controller:

(i) Hosting supplier: Microsoft Azure

(ii) Email processor: Wildbit, 225 Chestnut St, Philadelphia, PA 19106

(iii) Resume/CV Transforming: Box Privacy, 900 Jefferson Avenue, Redwood City, CA 94063

### **Right of Access**

Individuals may request to access, correct, amend or delete information we hold about them by contacting us here. Unless it is prohibited by law, we will remove any Personal Information about an individual, either you (our user) or a candidate, from our servers at your or their request. There is no charge for an individual to access or update their Personal Information. To obtain a copy of the personal information HireHive holds about you, please contact us at [support@hirehive.com](mailto:support@hirehive.com) This information will be supplied to you within 30 days.

### **Security**

HireHive recognizes your right to personal privacy and we take our security responsibilities seriously. We use a number of mechanisms to protect the security and integrity of your personal information. We make all reasonable efforts to safeguard and protect your personal information. We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

### **Right of Rectification or Erasure**

If you discover that we hold inaccurate information about you, you may request us to correct that information at any time.

If you have an account with us, you may access, correct, or request that we delete your personal data by logging into your account or by contacting us at support@hirehive.com. This request can include personal data of other individuals, like your employees or candidates that you have provided to us and who have requested this of you. We will respond to these requests within a reasonable timeframe of less than 30 days.

### **Cookies**

We use cookies on our website to collect information and improve our Services. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer. We may use “persistent cookies” to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Service. We may use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Service.

### **Retention**

We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of the purposes for which it was collected.

### **Opt-Out**

Our site provides users with the option to opt-in to receive promotional or marketing information from HireHive. If at any stage you would rather not receive marketing emails from us, please inform us by e-mail at [optout@hirehive.com](mailto:optout@hirehive.com) or click ‘Unsubscribe’ in any communication received from us.

### **Revisions to Privacy Statement**

HireHive may revise this privacy statement at any time. Changes to this privacy statement will be posted here so you should periodically check this page to review the most recent statement.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained to the highest standard.

### **Contact Information:**

HireHive  
3rd Floor, Republic of Work  
12 South Mall, Cork  
T12 RD43, Ireland
